# **Bozo Yasuo** (ブロックチェーン 開発者)

Email Address: <a href="mailto:c.john.number@gmail.com">c.john.number@gmail.com</a>

Skype ID: <u>briefman.new</u>

Telegram ID : <u>BY\_crypto\_dev</u>

Birthday: 1992. 5. 19

Address: 375-1003 Chiyoda-ku Street, Marunochi City in Tokyo, Japan

#### **Profile**

I am a skilled Blockchain developer with 6+ years of experience who has recently helped to develop and launch a series of decentralized applications (DAPP) publishing their data and interacting with the blockchain.

As a blockchain developer, I act as the important role in crafting, developing, testing, going live and maintaining the chain protocol.

# Work experience

03/2018 - 05/2022, Blockchain Developer, Pearl Data Firm, in Tokyo, Japan

- Worked on the development and implementation of new blockchain technologies and completed professional market research.
- Built and maintained strategic relationships with potential investors and business partners and brainstormed new ideas.
- Cooperated with colleagues from the other departments and participated in the creation and testing of new software and decentralized applications.

# Main Project

https://app.formation.fi
www.croxswap.com
www.vaultdefi.com
(Swap, Pool, Farm, Bridge on BSC, Ethereum) Form
(Swap, Liquidity, Pool, Farm on BSC mainnet) Crox
(Defi Info Education and Awareness) Vault

06/2015 - 02/2018, Blockchain Developer, CodeComplete Inc, in Meguro city, Japan

- Used Socket.io framework to create WebSocket, to connect with three different API's (Bitfinex, bitcoinaverage, fixer.io).
- Created Node.js middleware application server to encapsulate modern JS widget framework and NFT marketplace.
- Worked with business teams using Agile methodology to integrate business line of apps with SOA in a seamless fashion.

# Main Project

- https://luckychip.io

- www.artion.io

- www.pantherswap.com

(P2E, Swap, Stake, Lottery on BSC mainnet) LC

(NFT Marketplace on Fantom mainnet) Ftm

(Trade, Pool, Farm, Lottery on BSC mainnet) Panther

#### Education

09/2011 - 05/2015, Computer Engineering, Waseda University, Shinjuku in Japan

Graduated with Distinction (Grade 1 - A/excellent equivalent in all subjects)

GPA: 4.52 (Top 3% of the Program)

The 2015 Principal's Award winner for representing the school at multiple international engineering competitions

Clubs and Societies: Al Society, FinTech Society

04/2007 - 08/2011, Yamabuki High School, Shinjuku in Japan

Extracurricular Activities: Computer Club, Engineering Society

## **Skills**

### - Software Skills

Web3.js (wallet creation and connection), advanced Ethers.js

Smart Contracts (Solidity, Truffle and hardhat framework, ERC, BEP and EIP token release)

NFT minting, swap, bridge (cross chain network), staking (farm and pool)

React, Vue, Angular, Laravel, Node, Python (Flask, Django) - Front End

SQL (MySQL, SQLite, Postgres), NoSQL (MongoDB, Firebase,) - Back End

Strong DEFI and DEX tech knowledge (including interaction with Chainlink Oracle DB)

Familiar with AWS, Alchemy, Linux, Ubuntu OS environment

# - Languages

Japanese: Native

English: Fluently

Chinese: Intermediate

#### Certificates

06/2016, Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering

09/2019, Certified Blockchain Professional, JTC Council